getmyads.com 2016-10-17

# GetMyAds - Privacy

## WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

GetMyAds Company is truly committed for protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience. This privacy policy applies to the GetMyAds website and governs data collection, storage, usage and disclosure. By using the GetMyAds website, you consent to the data practices described in this policy. 

GetMyAds has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the GetMyAds website. 

By using the GetMyAds website and accepting the User Agreement you also agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you must not use the GetMyAds website. The terms "We," "Us," "Our," or "Company" includes GetMyAds Company and our affiliates. 

## DATA COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL/BANKING CREDENTIALS

1\. GetMyAds collects your information when you register on the GetMyAds website and when you visit GetMyAds page. 

2\. Personal Information: We may collect the following types of personal information in order to provide you with the use and access to the GetMyAds website, services and tools, and for any additional purposes set out in this Privacy Policy: 

  * Name, and contact information, such as email address, phone number, mobile telephone number, physical address, Birthday and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as bank account numbers; 
  * Transactional information based on your activities on the sites (such as , Buying, Advertising, item and content you generate or that relates to your account), and other information you provide to purchase token; 
  * Personal information you provide to us through correspondence, chats, dispute resolution, or shared by you from other social applications, services or websites; 
  * Additional personal information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself if we believe you are violating site policies (for example, we may ask you to send us an ID to answer additional questions online to help verify your identity); 
  * Information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising, including, but not limited to, device ID, device type, location, geo-location information, computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information. 

## USE & STORAGE OF YOUR INFORMATION

Personal information submitted via the Contact, Query and Registration forms on this site is sent via email to the relevant confidential staff only. The information is used to respond to a visitor's request either by email or phone if a phone number is provided. The information may be retained in our email system and contacts databases. We use anonymous web usage information to analyse how people use this site and to help direct improvements for the site. We aggregate this information in a way that does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, and other third-parties with which we have a business relationship. We will not sell this information. To the extent permitted by law, we may disclose the information that we collect (i) when required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency; or (ii) whenever we believe that disclosing such information is necessary or advisable, for example, to protect our rights, property, or safety, or those of others. If we, or any of our affiliated companies, are acquired, we expect that the collected information would be transferred along with the other business assets. 

## HOW WE USE COOKIES

We may use cookies to remember you across multiple visits to our site. We don’t sell cookie data to anyone. In addition to cookies that we might use on the site, others (like Google Analytics) may also serve cookies. If you do not wish cookies to be used in connection with your visit, please disable the cookie function in your browser or write to us. 

## ACCESSING AND MODIFYING YOUR INFORMATION

If you would like to request a copy of the information we hold about you, or make changes to that information, please write to us at info@getmyads.com. 

## THIS IS AN PHILIPPIANS WEB SITE

This website is operated in Philippines. If you are located outside of Philippines, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to Philippines. By using the website, or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer. 

## WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR EXTERNAL WEB SITES

This website may contain links to third-party websites such as our clients and partners. We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of these websites. As such, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those third-party websites. You should check the applicable third-party privacy policy and terms of use when visiting any other websites. 

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any changes on this page as soon as they go into effect. By accessing this website after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. 

## LODGING A COMPLAINT

If you believe we have not met our obligations under Philippians Privacy Law with regards to your personal information, please contact us on info@getmyads.com We treat such matters seriously. We will investigate as a priority, and will keep you informed as to the progress and outcome of our investigation. 

## HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at our official email address: info@getmyads.com.
